[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "What can you tell us about what's happened today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "Well, this came about as an unauthorized leak from somewhere in the investigation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "I mean, how credibly are people taking these police reports?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "Well, we do have the reaction from the family.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "Is it unfair towards George Zimmerman to be effectively declaring him guilty?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "Well, that is unfair to declare him guilty a month after the whole thing went down.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "Why is that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "Well, here's the thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NN", ",", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "What do you feel about a justice system that has that law?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "That \"Stand Your Ground\" thingy, that \"Stand Your Ground\" law that they have in place, I don't understand it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "If he then turns around and punches him, and you assume that happened, does that give anyone the right to shoot him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "CC", "NNS", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 173, "question": "What's it called?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "It's called \"Super Life.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "What did you feel when you heard that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "That was beautiful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "Do you think America is more or less racist since getting its first black president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "Well, you know, I think we've seen some things happening and some things being said about Obama that I think were sort of on the racist side.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "What do you think about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "I find that very interesting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "But should they be allowed to be vigilantes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "No, I really don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "Do you feel if it had been, for argument's sake, a 17- year-old white boy and a black man who had killed him, would we be in the same position?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "IN", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "DT", "CD", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "MD", "VB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "You really believe that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "I truly believe that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "Him actually using a gun?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", ",", "NN", ",", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "What do you say to him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "Well, please, son, be careful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "Isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "HAN: Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "And I understand that, is, you know, I mean, it took them three days to identify him, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "Ridiculous, too.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "And your purpose with this -- just remind me -- is to do what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "Is to raise awareness in children and adults and everybody that you can't judge a person by what he's wearing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "How's your etching and sketching?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "You shake it up like an Etch-a-Sketch.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "You have an Etch-a-Sketch?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "We're talking about big things here, folks.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "How big a problem is it going to be for Mitt Romney, if he becomes the nominee, the fact that his own health plans were very similar to what Barack Obama is trying to get through?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "Well, he should have problems in the Republican primary.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney", "Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "RB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "What do you make of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "You know, the question unfortunately can be answered by another question, which is the best thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "Is that what you're saying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "OLE: Well, not only the law that treats black boys.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "What do you think of everything that's happened in the last month?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "POS", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "First of all, I do want to thank you for giving me the opportunity to speak about this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Whitney"]}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "Did you try and help her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "VB", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "OLE: You know, I talked to Whitney.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Atlantic City"]}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ":", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "Can you relate to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "Oh my goodness, I had to cancel a New Years Eve show in Atlantic City a few years -- about two years ago.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "Could she still hit the big notes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "She hit some of them, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "Do you -- is your voice as good as it was, say, 20 years ago?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VB", ",", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ":", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "What do you feel watching that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "I'm just sad -- happy sad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "When you heard that Whitney had died, did you feel that it had been a wasted life or was it an inevitably short life that had amazingly high moments?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Whitney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 619, "question": "Or both?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 634, "question": "Of Whitney?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Whitney"]}}]